好啦  咱们可以上路了
Okay, we are good to go.
呃  你好像忘了一件事情嘛
Uh, I think we're forgetting one thing.
哦  对  对
Oh! Ha ha. Yes.
还没有涂唇彩呢
Lip gloss.
不  记录上写着你必须戴着眼镜
No, it says here you're required to wear glasses
才能开车
to drive.
是吗
Does it say that?
我只是拍照的时候会戴眼镜的
I thought I just needed those for the picture.
给我戴上你的眼镜
Put 'em on.
哦  天哪  我的眼睛
O. M. Eyeballs.
发动  换挡
Now start the car and put it in gear.
当然
Absolutely. ( Laughs )
如果您能  告诉我
If you could just... Direct me to the...
点火器在哪里
Ignition.
好像不能是吧
No?
启动了  很好
All right. This is good.
左转  前面有建筑物
Now merge left. There's construction ahead.
- 呃  - 左转  左转啊
- Uh... - Go left. I said left!
太快了太快了
Okay, too far, too far.
- 明白  - 垃圾桶
- Okay. - Garbage can.
我不知道
I don't...
现在
Okay.
停车
Pull the vehicle over.
呃  好的
Uh, uh, okay.
减速  减速
Slow down. Slow down!
- 我不  - 邮箱
- I'm not... I... - Mailbox.
- 邮箱啊  - 你在说啥
- Mailbox! - What?!
这样的话
So...
我过了吗
Pass?